# Cristan Kim Xavier Lansang

6 Salazar St. BF Homes Q.C · 09771725630

Email: ckxslo23@gmail.com

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Personable information technology student and a working professional with more than two years of hard-worked experience in giving amenable and satisfactory service in the BPO industry. Can smoothly solve communication challenges while focused on surpassing expectations.

## **Experience**

5/2021 - 10/2021

Community Manager • Blockhype

Coordinated and managed multiple crypto-communities, acting as both moderator and representative for contracted projects.

10/2019 - 5/2021

CSR • Research Analyst • Concentrix

Learned how to listen carefully to track customer interaction details in provided tools for feedback, problems, and record solutions offered.

5/2019 - 08/2019

TSR • Technical Support Representative • Teleperformance

Provided solutions. Brokedown and evaluated user problems, using test scripts, personal expertise, and probing questions.

### **Education**

Mapua University (MAKATI) 2019-Present

Address: 333 Sen. Gil J. Puyat Ave, Makati, 1200 Metro Manila

Bachelor of Science - Information Technology

Mapua University (INTRAMUROS) 2015-2019

658 Muralla St, Intramuros, Manila, 1002 Metro Manila

Bachelor of Science - Mechanical Engineering

#### **Notable Skills**

- Adaptability
- Creative Problem Solving
- English Proficiency (Excellent in understanding / Proficient Speaker)
- Tech-savvy
- Fundamental Analysis